{"sid": "AISBWO02XKG6_main", "calc_equals_delay": 3, "block_data": {"block_0": {"mean_level": 8, "start_time": 367032, "questions": {"q0": {"time_left_start": "300", "question_time_start": 367033, "question": "6+7+7+43", "correct_answer": 63, "events": [["submit", 378917]], "time_left_end": "289", "answered_time": 378917, "user_answer": "63", "user_correct": "True", "score": "1"}, "q1": {"time_left_start": "289", "question_time_start": 378917, "question": "4+3+6+13", "correct_answer": 26, "events": [["submit", 383215]], "time_left_end": "284", "answered_time": 383215, "user_answer": "26", "user_correct": "True", "score": "2"}, "q2": {"time_left_start": "284", "question_time_start": 383216, "question": "7+68+83", "correct_answer": 158, "events": [["submit", 388262]], "time_left_end": "279", "answered_time": 388262, "user_answer": "158", "user_correct": "True", "score": "3"}, "q3": {"time_left_start": "279", "question_time_start": 388262, "question": "4+24+17", "correct_answer": 45, "events": [["submit", 395525]], "time_left_end": "272", "answered_time": 395525, "user_answer": "45", "user_correct": "True", "score": "4"}, "q4": {"time_left_start": "272", "question_time_start": 395525, "question": "24+516", "correct_answer": 540, "events": [["submit", 400931]], "time_left_end": "267", "answered_time": 400931, "user_answer": "540", "user_correct": "True", "score": "5"}, "q5": {"time_left_start": "267", "question_time_start": 400932, "question": "34+873", "correct_answer": 907, "events": [["submit", 406353]], "time_left_end": "261", "answered_time": 406353, "user_answer": "907", "user_correct": "True", "score": "6"}, "q6": {"time_left_start": "261", "question_time_start": 406353, "question": "8+98+77", "correct_answer": 183, "events": [["calc_8", 413360], ["calc_5", 413891], ["calc_+", 415928], ["calc_9", 416698], ["calc_8", 417170], ["calc_=", 418123], ["submit", 423534]], "used_calculator": "True", "time_left_end": "244", "answered_time": 423534, "user_answer": "183", "user_correct": "True", "score": "7"}, "q7": {"time_left_start": "244", "question_time_start": 423534, "question": "78+37+23+47", "correct_answer": 185, "events": [["submit", 437398]], "time_left_end": "230", "answered_time": 437398, "user_answer": "185", "user_correct": "True", "score": "8"}, "q8": {"time_left_start": "230", "question_time_start": 437399, "question": "63+13", "correct_answer": 76, "events": [["submit", 441310]], "time_left_end": "226", "answered_time": 441310, "user_answer": "76", "user_correct": "True", "score": "9"}, "q9": {"time_left_start": "226", "question_time_start": 441310, "question": "38+83", "correct_answer": 121, "events": [["submit", 444456]], "time_left_end": "223", "answered_time": 444456, "user_answer": "121", "user_correct": "True", "score": "10"}}}, "block_1": {"mean_level": 8, "start_time": 444456, "questions": {"q0": {"time_left_start": "223", "question_time_start": 444456, "question": "69+223", "correct_answer": 292, "events": [["submit", 451360]], "time_left_end": "216", "answered_time": 451360, "user_answer": "292", "user_correct": "True", "score": "11"}, "q1": {"time_left_start": "216", "question_time_start": 451360, "question": "9+54+23", "correct_answer": 86, "events": [["submit", 458989]], "time_left_end": "209", "answered_time": 458989, "user_answer": "86", "user_correct": "True", "score": "12"}, "q2": {"time_left_start": "209", "question_time_start": 458989, "question": "7+7+7+58", "correct_answer": 79, "events": [["submit", 465468]], "time_left_end": "202", "answered_time": 465468, "user_answer": "79", "user_correct": "True", "score": "13"}, "q3": {"time_left_start": "202", "question_time_start": 465468, "question": "6+38+17", "correct_answer": 61, "events": [["submit", 473154]], "time_left_end": "194", "answered_time": 473154, "user_answer": "51", "user_correct": "False", "score": "12"}, "q4": {"time_left_start": "194", "question_time_start": 473154, "question": "73+58", "correct_answer": 131, "events": [["submit", 479581]], "time_left_end": "188", "answered_time": 479581, "user_answer": "131", "user_correct": "True", "score": "13"}, "q5": {"time_left_start": "188", "question_time_start": 479582, "question": "3+9+7+36", "correct_answer": 55, "events": [["submit", 488257]], "time_left_end": "179", "answered_time": 488257, "user_answer": "55", "user_correct": "True", "score": "14"}, "q6": {"time_left_start": "179", "question_time_start": 488257, "question": "58+94+57+93", "correct_answer": 302, "events": [["submit", 509762]], "time_left_end": "158", "answered_time": 509762, "user_answer": "252", "user_correct": "False", "score": "13"}, "q7": {"time_left_start": "158", "question_time_start": 509762, "question": "26+359", "correct_answer": 385, "events": [["submit", 519327]], "time_left_end": "148", "answered_time": 519327, "user_answer": "385", "user_correct": "True", "score": "14"}, "q8": {"time_left_start": "148", "question_time_start": 519327, "question": "4+57+68", "correct_answer": 129, "events": [["submit", 527270]], "time_left_end": "140", "answered_time": 527270, "user_answer": "129", "user_correct": "True", "score": "15"}, "q9": {"time_left_start": "140", "question_time_start": 527270, "question": "24+49", "correct_answer": 73, "events": [["submit", 531720]], "time_left_end": "136", "answered_time": 531720, "user_answer": "73", "user_correct": "True", "score": "16"}}}, "block_2": {"mean_level": 8, "start_time": 531720, "questions": {"q0": {"time_left_start": "136", "question_time_start": 531720, "question": "8+47+63", "correct_answer": 118, "events": [["submit", 540934]], "time_left_end": "127", "answered_time": 540934, "user_answer": "118", "user_correct": "True", "score": "17"}, "q1": {"time_left_start": "127", "question_time_start": 540935, "question": "74+38", "correct_answer": 112, "events": [["submit", 545727]], "time_left_end": "122", "answered_time": 545727, "user_answer": "112", "user_correct": "True", "score": "18"}, "q2": {"time_left_start": "122", "question_time_start": 545727, "question": "37+756", "correct_answer": 793, "events": [["submit", 553098]], "time_left_end": "114", "answered_time": 553098, "user_answer": "793", "user_correct": "True", "score": "19"}, "q3": {"time_left_start": "114", "question_time_start": 553099, "question": "9+39+19", "correct_answer": 67, "events": [["submit", 563806]], "time_left_end": "104", "answered_time": 563806, "user_answer": "67", "user_correct": "True", "score": "20"}, "q4": {"time_left_start": "104", "question_time_start": 563807, "question": "7+4+3+94", "correct_answer": 108, "events": [["submit", 571932]], "time_left_end": "96", "answered_time": 571932, "user_answer": "108", "user_correct": "True", "score": "21"}, "q5": {"time_left_start": "96", "question_time_start": 571932, "question": "8+7+8+89", "correct_answer": 112, "events": [["submit", 587240]], "time_left_end": "80", "answered_time": 587240, "user_answer": "112", "user_correct": "True", "score": "22"}, "q6": {"time_left_start": "80", "question_time_start": 587240, "question": "63+178", "correct_answer": 241, "events": [["submit", 593294]], "time_left_end": "74", "answered_time": 593294, "user_answer": "241", "user_correct": "True", "score": "23"}, "q7": {"time_left_start": "74", "question_time_start": 593295, "question": "47+19+36+96", "correct_answer": 198, "events": [["calc_4", 595814], ["calc_7", 596341], ["calc_+", 597262], ["calc_1", 597884], ["calc_9", 598693], ["calc_+", 600046], ["calc_3", 600662], ["calc_6", 601157], ["calc_+", 601678], ["calc_9", 602485], ["calc_6", 602949], ["calc_=", 603708], ["submit", 609272]], "used_calculator": "True", "time_left_end": "58", "answered_time": 609272, "user_answer": "198", "user_correct": "True", "score": "24"}, "q8": {"time_left_start": "58", "question_time_start": 609272, "question": "4+59+43", "correct_answer": 106, "events": [["submit", 615422]], "time_left_end": "52", "answered_time": 615422, "user_answer": "106", "user_correct": "True", "score": "25"}, "q9": {"time_left_start": "52", "question_time_start": 615422, "question": "58+38", "correct_answer": 96, "events": [["submit", 619399]], "time_left_end": "48", "answered_time": 619399, "user_answer": "96", "user_correct": "True", "score": "26"}}}, "block_3": {"mean_level": 8, "start_time": 619399, "questions": {"q0": {"time_left_start": "48", "question_time_start": 619399, "question": "8+79+18", "correct_answer": 105, "events": [["submit", 628645]], "time_left_end": "39", "answered_time": 628645, "user_answer": "105", "user_correct": "True", "score": "27"}, "q1": {"time_left_start": "39", "question_time_start": 628646, "question": "99+547", "correct_answer": 646, "events": [["submit", 633588]], "time_left_end": "34", "answered_time": 633588, "user_answer": "646", "user_correct": "True", "score": "28"}, "q2": {"time_left_start": "34", "question_time_start": 633588, "question": "39+589", "correct_answer": 628, "events": [["submit", 643217]], "time_left_end": "24", "answered_time": 643217, "user_answer": "628", "user_correct": "True", "score": "29"}, "q3": {"time_left_start": "24", "question_time_start": 643217, "question": "39+59+54+43", "correct_answer": 195, "events": []}}}}}